<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Persian</title>
    <link>https://www.example.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Persian</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://www.example.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AJ Mitchell</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/author/john-doe_am/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/author/john-doe_am/</guid>
      <description>Please contact me with further inquiries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>examples</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/post/examples/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/post/examples/</guid>
      <description>Introductory BlurbBecause of time, I had to remove the code itself from this HTML document. I think I learned a solid lesson about choosing a proper Hugo Theme that will be best for my purposes. I really like the persian theme but it does not appear to be good for showing .rmd chunks for translating how the ggplot was generated below.
I appreciate this lesson a great deal because I think this will be an extremely valuable way to present my CV and visualizations that I have made for lab and publications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/post/post-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/post/post-2/</guid>
      <description>“And I knew exactly what to do. But in a much more real sense, I had no idea what to do.” – Michael Scott.
 Publications
Articles
Parr, Lisa A., Thomas Mitchell, and Erin Hecht. Intranasal oxytocin in rhesus monkeys alters brain networks that detect social salience and reward. American journal of primatology 80.10 (2018): e22915.
Eric Feczko, TA Mitchell, Hasse Walum, Jenna M. Brooks, Thomas R. Heitz, Larry J.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/post/am_post-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/post/am_post-1/</guid>
      <description>My Research I am in the lab of Dr. Elinor Sullivan and co-mentored by Dr. Damien Fair at the Universtiy of Minnesota.
My research focuses on understanding the effects of the overconsumption of a high-fat diet during pregnancy. Specifically, my work is dedicated to understanding how this effects fetal neurodevelopment and social outcomes.
 I focus on understanding how diet and obesity impact the immune response during pregnancy, and then how these changes related to offspring social outcomes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Water, Dogs, &amp; Bikes</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/post/post-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/post/post-3/</guid>
      <description> Whoaa - Keanu Reeves
 </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
